[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：练习八旨在让你获得一点
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Exercise eight is designed to get you a little bit of
练习玩弄流的概念，以及
practice playing around with the notion of streams, and
做出自己的流响应。
making your own stream responses.
让我快速引导你练习八。
Let me quickly orient you exercise eight.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你会注意到练习八从一个按钮开始
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You'll notice that exercise eight starts out with a button
和一个列表，然后您将订阅我们在这里使用的jQuery单击事件
and a list, and you're gonna subscribe to the click event we're using jQuery here
只是为了让事情变得简单。
just to make things simple.
所以你不用担心DOM东西。
So you don't have to worry about DOMstuff.
我们将订阅该按钮上的单击事件，并且
We're gonna subscribe to the click event on that button, and
那我们就做点什么。
then we're gonna do something.
这就是你必须弄清楚怎么做的事情。
And it's that something that you're gonna have to figure out how to do.
但在我们的应用程序的其他地方，这是在第九行，
But elsewhere in our app, that is down on line nine,
我们要听一个序列，它将是一个采样序列。
we're gonna listen to a sequence that's gonna be a sampled sequence.
这就是我的意思。
So this is what I mean.
采样是基于时间的东西。
Sampling is a time based thing.
所以，假设你非常快地点击了按钮。
So let's say you click the button really, really fast.
我只想每500毫秒听一个事件。
I only wanna hear a single event every 500 milliseconds.
我想节流，
I wanna throttle that stream,
所以我会有一个快速到来的数据流，向下发送一大堆数据。
so I'm gonna have a stream that's coming fast to send in a bunch of data down.
但我想创建一个合成的流
But I wanna create a composed stream that
每500毫秒只发送一个事件给我。
only sends me out an event ever 500 milliseconds.
并忽略并丢弃所有那些来得太快的重复。
And ignores and drops all those repetitive ones that are coming too fast.
我想订阅这个样本流，并且
And I wanna subscribe to that sampled stream, and
将这些消息拖放到列表框中。
drop those messages into the list box.
所以只是想直观地告诉你会期待什么。
So just to show you visually what you're gonna be expecting.
让我弹出练习八的固定版本，就这样
Let me pop up the fixed version of exercise eight, just so
你在视觉上明白你想要的是什么。
you visually understand what you're trying to go for here.
因此，如果我点击“点击我”，它会向其中添加一条消息。
So if I click the click me, it adds a single message to it.
再次单击它，它将添加另一条消息。
Click it again, it adds another message.
但如果我开始快速点击它，
But if I start clicking it really fast,
您会注意到，我每500毫秒只收到一个事件。
you'll notice that I'm only getting one event every 500 milliseconds.
好了，就这样，这就是我们要做的。
Okay, that's it, that's all we're doing.
你在玩弄如何让自己设定一个固定的时间间隔，
You play around with how you can set yourself up with a set interval,
然后对一条小溪进行采样，看看你能想出什么。
and sample a stream and see what you come up with.
所以我们会花大约，让我们把这15分钟给你玩一下。
So we'll take about, let's call this 15 minutes for you to play around with this.
代码不多。
It's not a lot of code.
如果您需要一些提示，请查看修复版本。
If you need some hints, look at the fixed version.
但这应该让你的大脑开始思考事件作为我们的模式
But this should get your brain starting to think about events as our pattern
用于异步。
for async.